convertmedia.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy – Website | ConvertMedia

## Website Privacy Policy

Last updated: August 30, 2012

ConvertMedia, Inc ( **“ConvertMedia” “we”, “our”** or **“us”** ) respects the privacy of the users of its website at [convertmedia.com](http://www.convertmedia.com/) (the **“Site”** ) and is committed to protect the information it collects and/or is disclosed to it by the users of this Site ( **“users”** or **“you”** ). 

This privacy policy is in reference to the use of our Site; if you wish to review the privacy policy for use of our media buying Platform and related Services, please [click here](http://convertmedia.com/privacy-platform/ "ActiveMail Privacy Policy").

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that ConvertMedia does not own or control or to people it does not employ or manage.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

ConvertMedia collects information from our users at several different points on our Site. This may include traffic data including a user’s IP address, domain server, type of computer, and type of web browser. This is anonymous information that does not personally identify a user but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving a user’s experience on the Site. 

In general, when you visit our Site you remain anonymous. Some areas of our Site may however require login/registration. Personal information, such as a user’s name, address, contact information and other personally-identifiable information ( **“Personal Information”** ) may be collected from you and stored in our databases, typically when you register to the Site, request support, enter into a sales promotion or otherwise interact with us (for example through the “contact us” option). It should be made clear that you have no legal obligation to provide us with any Personal Information and the submission of such information is entirely subject to your sole discretion and consent. However if you will not provide us with the required information we may not be able to provide you with the information/services requested by you. Registered users may have a user name and password to access their information.

We may also collect statistical and other data related to your use of the Site or services thereon as well as information on Site usage patterns. This information is collected and used as non-individually identifiable information.

Any Personal Information voluntarily disclosed by you on our Site through e-mail, in public-view personal profiles, public-view uploaded materials, chat rooms, message boards, or intra-Site message systems, is viewed and possibly used by other users, and such disclosure may have unintended privacy implications for you.

**HOW WE USE INFORMATION**

We use information which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Site and improve our services, to track users’ movements around the Site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may use the information collected to market directly to that person subject to requirements of applicable law. This non personal information may be shared with third parties.

We compile and store data and information and generate reports related to our users’ access to and use of our Site and services.

We also use your user information for providing a better experience on the Site and to improve our client services and for providing communications related to our Site, platform and Services, including for the following: (i) process and reply of your requests, (ii) obtain consents to provide and provide marketing materials, promotions and/or offerings (iii) support related issues, notices about updates, new features, or other information of interest to our users regarding the above. You may opt-out of receiving our marketing information by following instructions included in our marketing/promotional e-mails or by changing the appropriate account settings in our Site. 

By using our Site you agree and allow us to use the information you provide us with for sending you marketing materials regarding our services and/or products, promotions and/or offerings including by email or other reasonable communication method.

To the extent required under applicable data processing laws and regulations, any personal information that we collect will be stored in our database and will be used in accordance with such applicable laws and regulations.

We do not share, distribute, sell or rent any of your Personal Information with/to third parties, except in the following circumstances:

– If the information is required by law in order to prevent, investigate, or take action regarding illegal activities, situations involving potential threats to physical safety, rights, property or of any person, suspected fraud and violations of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use. In addition, we will share information in response to legal process, court orders, subpoenas, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

– For the purpose of providing and operating the Site we may share non-PII information with trusted third-party partners who need to know for purpose of providing Site-related services to us only (and not for such third parties’ commercial use in any way). We will require that these third parties comply with this Privacy Policy and/or with privacy policies at least as protective as this Privacy Policy. 

– If we have your permission to do so.

Any data processing performed by these third parties will, if and when required by law, be governed by a data processing agreement in the form required by law, preserving your statutory data protection rights.

**BUSINESS TRANSFERS**

In the conduct of our business, we may sell certain of our assets. Information collected from users of the Site, including personal information, could be transferred as part of such transaction. By submitting your Personal Information through the Site, you agree that your information may be transferred to third parties under such or similar circumstances. 

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Site. We use cookies to enhance the user experience of our Site by means such as storing password or user preference information. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our Site with the only drawback being the disablement of some of the usability features of our Site. We may also use cookies to track and monitor usage of the Site by users for the purposes of marketing and Site improvement. The data collected from these cookies will never be shared with an external source and will be used for internal purposes only. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. [Click here](http://optout.admailtiser.com/OptoutServlet) to Opt-Out. 

ConvertMedia uses the Evidon assurance platform to comply with the cross-industry Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising as managed by the **Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA)**. As part of this service, ConvertMedia’s online advertisements are sometimes delivered with icons that help consumers understand how their data is being used and provide choice options to consumers that want more control.

To opt-out from behavioral advertising in general, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**TRACKING PIXELS**

We employ a software technology called tracking pixels that helps us better manage content on our web site as well as in order to show our users ads or promotions or marketing materials related to our users at a later stage. Tracking pixels are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, tracking pixels are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. 

**E-MAIL COMMUNICATIONS**

At any time, you have the ability to opt out of receiving marketing communications from ConvertMedia, but you may not opt out of administrative emails (for example, emails about your transactions or policy changes) while you are a registered user. You can opt out by either changing your e-mail preferences or using the link provided at the bottom of each email message. 

We do not send emails to anyone without permission, and we do not sell or rent email addresses to any unauthorized third party. This does not mean that we can prevent spam from happening on the Internet. If you believe that you have received an unsolicited email from us, please contact us at the e-mail below and we will investigate. 

**POLICY TOWARDS CHILDREN**

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@ConvertMedia.com](mailto:privacy@ConvertMedia.com). If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

**SECURITY**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, due to the nature of Internet communications and evolving technologies, unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, the security of user information may be compromised at any time. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.

Therefore, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of Personal Information and disclaim any assurance that such information will remain free from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties who, despite our efforts, obtain unauthorized access.

**CHANGES AND CONSENT TO PRIVACY POLICY**

By registering with ConvertMedia or by using the Site without prior registration, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change the provisions of the Privacy Policy from time to time and you are therefore advised to check it regularly. Your continued use of the Site after any change to the policy constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

**LINKS**

Our Site may have links to the sites of other companies. We are not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

**UPDATE/DELETE USER INFORMATION**

You can write to us at any time to obtain a copy of your information and to have any inaccuracies corrected or if you no longer desire our service (in which case we will endeavor to remove your personal data provided to us). Where appropriate, you may have your Personal Information erased, rectified, amended or completed. In order to contact us regarding your information please e-mail [privacy@ConvertMedia.com](mailto:privacy@ConvertMedia.com). 

To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections, however, you should protect your password from disclosure because anyone who gains access to your password may have access to, and may edit, your profile.

**GOVERNING LAW**

This Privacy Policy shall be exclusively governed by and construed in all respects under the laws of Israel, without giving effect to any choice-of-law or conflict-of-law provisions. Any and all legal claims, suits or actions that arise in connection with this Privacy Policy or with breach of this Privacy Policy shall be submitted to the personal jurisdiction of the courts located in the courts of New York, New York.
